JONATHAN SANDERS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

■ jonsandersss@gmail.com ② j10sanders.github.io S 917-538-7146 NYC in jonathan-sanders-b2488649 ① j10sanders

SUMMARY

I left my (React) frontend developer role at Bank of America to start a business called Dimpull. I'm passionate about building a great company with great culture. I enjoy using React and Web3 technologies, and have fullstack experience.

EMPLOYMENT

Dimpull

Founder · Apr 2018 to Current · NYC

- Created Dimpull, a blockchain education marketplace (dimpull.com).
- I used a React frontend and a Python backend with PostgreSQL.
- Dimpull uses Web3 technologies such as Truffle, Solidity, and various other tools for accepting payments into an Ethereum escrow smart contract that I wrote.
- Payments are automatically transferred from the smart contract, dependent on call information delivered by Twilio's API at the close of a call.

Bank of America

Software Developer - Assistant Vice President · Jan 2017 to Apr 2018 · NYC

- Hired to do Python-based web development, but quickly promoted to a new team devoted to building out new Javascript/React based frontends.
- Lead developer of the first React app to go live at BoA: a blotter for swaps traders which uses websockets for real-time
- Contributed to a drag-drop library for OpenFin (similar to Electron's) and a performant internal grid library.
- Managed team of remote developers, and guided them on best practices in React.
- Taught the git workflow to the teams using our new stack.
- Promoted to Assistant Vice President.

Recurse Center

Participant · Oct 2016 to Dec 2016 · NYC

- Built winthemini (github.com/j10sanders/WinTheMini): a social network for people who do the NYT Mini Crossword
- winthemini used Python, Flask, Postgres, and SQLAlchemy.
- Contributed to open source projects like proselint and pyradio.

Access Softek

Developer, Tech Support Manager, and PM · Apr 2014 to Sep 2016 · NYC

- Developed Python scripts to monitor hundreds of APIs and internal services.
- Managed NYC tech support team and all Online Banking tech support.
- Managed projects such as making apps ADA compliant and a large migration of our internal ticket system.

Helm

Assistant to CEO and Software Developer · Mar 2012 to May 2014 · NYC

- Using Ruby on Rails, built out our web architecture for inviting CEOs and collecting their information for "roundtables" and summits.
- Built our CRM using Google Docs and early Zapier API.

EDUCATION

NYU 2009-2013

Bachelor's Philosophy

ACTIVITIES